Guide to Speeches in the Records of the Office of the President (Dr. John Brademas) RG 3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - Harvard-Epworth Church Sermons (Cambridge, MA), 7 September 1986 (Box 619, Folder 102)
  - Background material for meeting with Ned Schnurman (NYC), 8 September 1986 (Box 620, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254675
  - Welcome remarks delivered at a Washington Square Park meeting (NYC), 9 September 1986 (Box 620, Folder 2)
  - Student Convocation, NYU, 15 September 1986 (Box 620, Folder 3)
  - "The Value of Public Service," delivered at a Brookings Institute Conference (Washington, D.C.), 16 September 1986 (Box 620, Folder 4)
  - Introduction of Terry Sanford at a breakfast at the Regency Hotel (NYC), 16 September 1986 (Box 620, Folder 5)
  - Aquino Lecture, NYU, 19 September 1986 (Box 620, Folder 6)
  - Lotos Club Dinner (NYC), 22 September 1986 (Box 620, Folder 7)
  - Welcome remarks delivered at an Alumni Council meeting, NYU, 22 September 1986 (Box 620, Folder 9)
  - Brief remarks delivered at a Graduate School of Business Administration Overseers dinner, NYU, 25 September 1986 (Box 620, Folder 10)
  - "The Value of Liberal Arts," delivered at Franklin Pierce College (NH), 27 September 1986 (Box 620, Folder 11)
  - NYC School Volunteer Program, 30 September 1986 (Box 620, Folder 12)
  - Nancy Hanks Dedication (Washington, D.C.), 6 October 1986 (Box 620, Folder 14)
  - University Senate meeting, NYU, 9 October 1986 (Box 620, Folder 15)
  - Sir Curtis Keeble Dinner, NYU, 15 October 1986 (Box 620, Folder 16)
  - Breakfast for orientation leaders, NYU, 16 October 1986 (Box 620, Folder 17)
  - 127th Annual Session of the American Dental Association (Miami Beach, FL), 19 October 1986 (Box 620, Folder 18)
  - Florida Alumni Leader Organizational Luncheon (Miami Beach, FL), 19 October 1986 (Box 620, Folder 19)
  - NYU School of Dentistry Alumni in Florida (Miami Beach, FL), 20 October 1986 (Box 620, Folder 21)
  - Press conference for temporary closing of Washington Square Park, 22 October 1986 (Box 620, Folder 22)
  - "Is the Agenda for Science Too Important to be Left to Scientists?" Sigma Xi Annual Meeting (Washington, D.C.), 25 October 1986 (Box 620, Folder 23)
  - NYSERNET Press Conference, NYU, 28 October 1986 (Box 620, Folder 24)
  - Interview with Al Scardino of The New York Times, 29 October 1986 (Box 620, Folder 25)
  - "The American Economy: The Political Dimension", 92nd St. Y, 29 October 1986 (Box 620, Folder 26)
  - Dedication for the William S. & Frances B. Todman Center for Film & Television, NYU, 30 October 1986 (Box 620, Folder 27)
  - Dental School Fall Alumni Day, NYU, 31 October 1986 (Box 620, Folder 28)
  - School of Business and Public Administration Charles Waldo Haskins Dinner honoring John C. Whitehead (NYC), 5 November 1986 (Box 620, Folder 29)
  - Tribute to Louis Koenig, 7 November 1986 (Box 620, Folder 31)
  - The Fulbright Alumni Association of Greater New York (NYC), 8 November 1986 (Box 620, Folder 32)
  - Parents Day, NYU, Nov 9, 1986 (Box 620, Folder 33)
  - Grantmakers in the Arts Second National Conference (NYC), 12 November 1986 (Box 620, Folder 34)
  - Introductory remarks preceding a lecture by Sir Ernst Gombrich, NYU, 17 November 1986 (Box 620, Folder 35)
  - Remarks introducing honorary degree recipients at a dinner honoring the 100th anniversary of the Graduate School of Arts and Science, NYU, 19 November 1986 (Box 620, Folder 36)
  - GSAS 100th Anniversary Convocation, NYU, 19 November 1986 (Box 620, Folder 37)
  - "Tax Reform in America: The Impact on Higher Education," delivered at a symposium on business sponsored by St. Peter's College (Jersey City, NJ), 19 November 1986 (Box 620, Folder 38)
  - Scanlan Dinner, 25 November 1986 (Box 620, Folder 40)
  - Kinnock Dinner, 1 December 1986 (Box 620, Folder 41)
  - Saul Bellow Introduction, NYU, 4 December 1986 (Box 620, Folder 42)
  - Brief remarks before a meeting of the Sports & Recreation Committee, NYU, 5 December 1986 (Box 620, Folder 43)
  - Essay on federal support for higher education for Scholarship & Public Policy Humanities Council, 9 December 1986 (Box 620, Folder 45)
  - Brief remarks at a Department of Hebrew & Judaic Studies dinner, NYU, 11 December 1986 (Box 620, Folder 46)
  - Meeting of the University Senate, NYU, 11 December 1986 (Box 620, Folder 47)
  - New York Times interview, 11 December 1986 (Box 620, Folder 48)
  - "Meanwhile Greece Goes on Travelling…" (Cambridge, MA), 12 December 1986 (Box 620, Folder 49)
  - Brief remarks at a dinner honoring major donors, NYU, 16 December 1986 (Box 620, Folder 50)
  - NY Public Library Lecture (NYC), 6 January 1987 (Box 620, Folder 51)
  - Highlights of the presidency of John Brademas, 10 January 1987 (Box 620, Folder 53)
  - Forbes response to article by Peter Brimelow, 23 January 1987 (Box 620, Folder 54)
  - Sigma Xi of Terre Haute Reception (Terre Haute, IN), 26 January 1997 (Box 620, Folder 55)
  - "Scholarship of Public Policy" (Terre Haute, IN), 26 January 1987 (Box 620, Folder 56)
  - Introduction to NYU staff handbook, 27 January 1987 (Box 620, Folder 57)
  - "The Role of Congress in Foreign Policy: Reflections of a Former Congressman" (Terre Haute, IN), 27 January 1987 (Box 620, Folder 58)
  - Remarks delivered at Indiana State University Founders Day (Terre Haute, IN), 27 January 1987 (Box 620, Folder 59)
  - Welcome remarks delivered at the National Book Critics Circle Awards Ceremony, NYU, 29 January 1987 (Box 620, Folder 61)
  - WABC Talk Radio interview (NYC), 1 February 1987 (Box 620, Folder 62)
  - Journal of Int'l Law & Politics Symposium: Trade Sanctions & Int'l Relations, NYU, 5 February 1987 (Box 620, Folder 63)
  - "National Priorities in Higher Education," National Association of Independent Colleges & Universities (Washington, D.C.), 6 February 1987 (Box 620, Folder 64)
  - Testimony offered before the Committee on Education and Labor (Washington, D.C.), 10 February 1987 (Box 620, Folder 66)
  - Citizens Committee, New Yorker for NY Awards (NYC), 12 February 1987 (Box 620, Folder 67)
  - University Senate Meeting, NYU, 12 February 1987 (Box 620, Folder 68)
  - "Is the Agenda for Science Too Important To Be Left To Scientists?" Sigma Xi article for American Scientist, 15 February 1987 (Box 620, Folder 69)
  - Brief remarks delivered befor the Consulate-General of the People's Republic of China (NYC), 17 February 1987 (Box 620, Folder 70)
  - Democratic National Committee National Finance Council (Newport Beach, CA), 21 February 1987 (Box 620, Folder 71)
  - NYU AIDS Mental Health Project Press Conference, NYU, 24 February 1987 (Box 620, Folder 72)
  - Remarks introducing Italian minister Spadolini, NYU, 25 February 1987 (Box 620, Folder 73)
  - 2nd Annual Petrie Lecture in Entrepreneurship, NYU, 26 February 1987 (Box 620, Folder 74)
  - "International Education: A Matter of Survival," article for Education Record, 27 February 1987 (Box 620, Folder 75)
  - University article on Dr. Brademas in Oxford, March 1987 (Box 620, Folder 76)
  - Lunch for Peter Lax, NYU, March 1987 (Box 620, Folder 78)
  - David Kriser Dinner (NYC), 4 March 1987 (Box 620, Folder 79)
  - Afternoon at Washington Square, NYU, 8 March 1987 (Box 620, Folder 80)
  - NYU in Albany Alumni Reception (Albany, NY), 9 March 1987 (Box 620, Folder 81)
  - Metro Center Benefit Luncheon, NYU, 10 March 1987 (Box 620, Folder 82)
  - Presidential, University & Ed. Scholars Breakfast, NYU, 10 March 1987 (Box 620, Folder 83)
  - "NYU: University in the City," delivered at the New-York Historical Society, 11 March 1987 (Box 620, Folder 84)
  - "Modern Role of Congress," delivered at the Association of the Bar Forum (NYC), 12 March 1987 (Box 620, Folder 85)
  - University Senate Meeting, NYU, 12 March 1987 (Box 620, Folder 86)
  - Introduction of Mr. Cuomo, Arms Control Forum, NYU, 16 March 1987 (Box 620, Folder 88)
  - Brief remarks at a press conference for "Due Case," NYU, 16 March 1987 (Box 620, Folder 89)
  - GPA Dean's Day, NYU, 16 March 1987 (Box 620, Folder 90)
  - Lynne Cheney press conference, NYU, 16 March 1987 (Box 620, Folder 91)
  - Dinner honoring Lady Warnock, NYU, 17 March 1987 (Box 620, Folder 92)
  - Real Estate Institute Leadership Award Dinner, NYU, 18 March 1987 (Box 620, Folder 93)
  - Hoosiers Dinner, NYU, 19 March 1987 (Box 620, Folder 94)
  - Meetings with alumni in Chicago and Los Angeles, 26-29 March 1987 (Box 621, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254683
  - Onassis Center For Hellenic Studies Convocation, NYU, 30 March 1987 (Box 621, Folder 2)
  - "Scholarships and Public Policy," essay for book on the humanities, 1 April 1987 (Box 621, Folder 3)
  - NY Academy of Sciences (NYC), 1 April 1987 (Box 621, Folder 4)
  - NY Science Policy Association (NYC), 1 April 1987 (Box 621, Folder 5)
  - Testimony before Committee on Gov't Affairs (Washington, D.C.), 2 April 1987 (Box 621, Folder 6)
  - New England Alumni Brunch (Boston, MA), 5 April 1987 (Box 621, Folder 7)
  - Introductory remarks at a dinner honoring and lecture given by Gerald Aylmer, NYU, 6 April 1987 (Box 621, Folder 8)
  - ACE Letter - Saunders, 7 April 1987 (Box 621, Folder 9)
  - Introductory remarks, Stephen J., Sr. & Beatrice Brademas Lecture (Muncie, IN), 13 April 1987 (Box 621, Folder 12)
  - Brief remarks to the Greek Fulbright Alumni Association (Greece), 28 April 1987 (Box 621, Folder 13)
  - "Fulbright at 40: Forging the Ties that Bind," Fulbright Distingusished Fellows Lecture (Greece), 29 April 1987 (Box 621, Folder 14)
  - Brief remarks delivered at a dinner honoring the American School of Classical Studies (Greece), 30 April 1987 (Box 621, Folder 15)
  - "Message from the President," Staff & Faculty Handbook, NYU, 4 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 16)
  - University of Athens (Greece), 4 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 17)
  - "Facing the Competition in Brainpower," address delivered at the 20th Annual Conference on the NYC Economy, 6 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 19)
  - President's Council Reception, NYU, 7 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 20)
  - Notre Dame speech, 9 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 21)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a dinner celebrating the Tisch School of the Arts, NYU, 11 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 22)
  - Brief remarks at the dedication of the Paulette Goddard Staircase, NYU, 11 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 23)
  - NY Academy of Public Education (NYC), 12 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 25)
  - Wagner Labor Dinner, NYU, 13 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 26)
  - Leonard Stern Hall Dedication, NYU, 14 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 27)
  - University Senate, NYU, 14 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 28)
  - Brief remarks delivered at a symposium sponsored by the Humanities Council, NYU, 15 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 29)
  - Washington D.C. alumni brunch, 17 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 30)
  - Bobst Awards in Arts & Letters, NYU, 19 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 31)
  - 25-Year Service Awards, NYU, 20 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 32)
  - Foreign Broadcasters Seminar, NYU, 21 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 33)
  - NYU Community Fund, 21 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 34)
  - Gallatin Association Leadership Breakfast (NYC), 27 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 35)
  - Alumni Council Annual Meeting, NYU, 28 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 36)
  - Walter Nichols Award to James D. Robinson III, NYU, 29 May 1987 (Box 621, Folder 37)
  - United Jewish Appeal (NYC), 1 June 1987 (Box 621, Folder 38)
  - Presidential citation awarded to Dr. Kobayashi, Graduate School of Business Administration Pre-Commencement Ceremony, NYU, 2 June 1987 (Box 621, Folder 39)
  - NY Congressional Delegation (Washington, D.C.), 3 June 1987 (Box 621, Folder 41)
  - Trustees Dinner celebrating honorary degree recipients, NYU, 4 June 1987 (Box 621, Folder 42)
  - Educational Press Association (Washington, D.C.), 4 June 1987 (Box 621, Folder 43)
  - Alumni Commencement Breakfast, NYU, 5 June 1987 (Box 621, Folder 44)
  - Remarks of Dr. Brademas and Mr. Tisch, NYU Commencement & Trustee Dinner, 5 June 1987 (Box 621, Folder 45)
  - 155th NYU Commencement, 5 June 1987 (Box 621, Folder 46)
  - BPA Entrepreneur of the Year Award Dinner, NYC, 6 June 1987 (Box 621, Folder 47)
  - Hospitality Industry (NYC), 9 June 1987 (Box 621, Folder 48)
  - Abraham Gitlow Chair in Business Administration, NYU, 10 June 1987 (Box 621, Folder 49)
  - University of Athens, 12 June 1987 (Box 621, Folder 50)
  - Sackler Wing at Met (NYC), 17 June 1987 (Box 621, Folder 51)
  - Ecumenical Doxology Homily (NYC), 4 July 1987 (Box 621, Folder 52)
  - "Congress & American Foreign Policy: The Lessons of Irangate," delivered at the Atlantic Institute (Paris, France), 6 July 1987 (Box 621, Folder 53)
  - Introductory remarks, Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner (Indianapolis, IN), 28 July 1987 (Box 621, Folder 54)
  - Article in the American Scientist, 30 July 1987 (Box 621, Folder 55)
  - Tribute to Joseph E. Levine (NYC), 3 August 1987 (Box 621, Folder 56)
  - Encyclopedia of NYC Endorsement (NYC), 14 August 1987 (Box 621, Folder 57)
  - Article about Fulbright Distinguished Fellows for PS magazine, 31 August 1987 (Box 621, Folder 58)
  - Student Convocation, NYU, 14 September 1987 (Box 621, Folder 59)
  - Inauguration, Jewish Theological Seminary, 14 September 1987 (Box 621, Folder 60)
  - Remarks delivered as part of a panel discussion on the bicentennial of the Constitution, Center for Strategic & International Studies (Washington, D.C.), 15 September 1987 (Box 621, Folder 61)
  - Remarks on the role of Congress in American foreign policy, delivered before the National Council of Jewish Women (NYC), 17 September 1987 (Box 621, Folder 62)
  - Remarks on higher education delivered at a convocation at Clark University (Worcester, MA), 18 September 1987 (Box 621, Folder 63)
  - Remarks on leisure, delivered before the Society of Park & Recreation Educators (New Orleans, LA), 20 September 1987 (Box 621, Folder 64)
  - Welcome Back Party, NYU, 21 September 1987 (Box 621, Folder 65)
  - Doxology about Greek heritage and the U.S. Constitution, delivered at the Greek Orthodox Archdiocesan Cathedral of the Holy Trinity, 27 September 1987 (Box 621, Folder 67)
  - Welcome remarks delivered at a luncheon honoring Wu Xueqian, Pratt House Council on Foreign Relations, 29 September 1987 (Box 621, Folder 68)
  - Remarks on improving U.S.-Poland foreign relations at a luncheon honoring Orzechowski, NYU, 30 September 1987 (Box 621, Folder 69)
  - Script for a taping for Methodist television, NYU, 6 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 70)
  - Welcome remarks delivered at a reception for new graduate students, NYU, 6 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 72)
  - Remarks about the School of Business and Public Administration delivered at the Haskins Award Dinner, 7 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 73)
  - Introduction for book, Group Portrait, written by S. Groenning, 7 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 74)
  - Article on the importance of NYU to Manhattan, published in the New York Observer, 13 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 75)
  - Remarks on the role of Congress in American foreign policy, delivered at the Iona College Fall Honors Convocation, 18 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 76)
  - Introductory remarks delivered at the Graduate School of Business Administration Overseers' Dinner, 19 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 77)
  - Breakfast for NYU Orientation Leaders, 19 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 78)
  - Joint Leaders of America Alumni Breakfast, 20 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 80)
  - Remarks on learned societies, delivered before the American Antiquarian Society (Worcester, MA), 21 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 81)
  - All-University Convocation, NYU, 22 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 82)
  - Remarks on education delivered as the NYS School Boards Association Annual Convention Speech, 23 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 83)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Associates Annual Awards Dinner, 24 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 84)
  - FAS newsletter, 27 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 85)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a National Broadcasting Seminar, NYU, 27 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 86)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration Annual Awards Dinner (NYC), 27 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 87)
  - 40th Anniversary of the Institute of Environmental Medicine, NYU Medical Center, 29 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 88)
  - Remarks on the role of Congress in American foreign policy, delivered before the Carnegie Council on Ethics & International Affairs, 30 October 1987 (Box 621, Folder 89)
  - Metro Center Press Conference, NYU, 2 November 1987 (Box 621, Folder 90)
  - Metro Center Press Conference, NYU, 2 November 1987 (Box 621, Folder 91)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the University Senate, NYU, 12 November 1987 (Box 621, Folder 92)
  - Remarks on arts and public policy, delivered at a meeting of the Federation of State Humanities Councils (Chicago, IL), 14 November 1987 (Box 621, Folder 93)
  - Trustees Scholar Dinner, NYU, 19 November 1987 (Box 621, Folder 94)
  - Keynote address delivered at a meeting of the Association for Higher Education (Baltimore, MD), 22 November 1987 (Box 621, Folder 95)
  - Remarks on the politics of education, delivered at a Harvard Education Seminar, 23 November 1987 (Box 621, Folder 96)
  - Memorandum about education, written to the 41st President, December 1987 (Box 621, Folder 97)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at the Fourth Estate Dinner, 2 December 1987 (Box 621, Folder 98)
  - The Century Association, Century Club, 3 December 1987 (Box 621, Folder 99)
  - Remarks announcing the creation of a master's degree in real estate in the School of Continuing Education, 7 December 1987 (Box 621, Folder 102)
  - Dinner at Leeds House, 8 December 1987 (Box 621, Folder 103)
  - Remarks delivered at the Proskauer Award Dinner honoring Arthur L. Linman (NYC), 9 December 1987 (Box 621, Folder 104)
  - President's Council Reception, NYU, 10 December 1987 (Box 621, Folder 105)
  - Billington Lecture, 10 December 1987 (Box 621, Folder 106)
  - National Education Association/School of Education, Health, Nursing, and the Arts Professions press luncheon, NYU, 14 December 1987 (Box 621, Folder 107)
  - Luncheon honoring librarians, NYU, 15 December 1987 (Box 621, Folder 108)
  - Remarks on NYU Libraries, 15 December 1987 (Box 621, Folder 109)
  - Mrs. Bobst's remarks at the Libraries Convocation, NYU, 15 December 1987 (Box 621, Folder 110)
  - Libraries Convocation, NYU, 15 December 1987 (Box 621, Folder 111)
  - Script and instructions relating to the Libraries Convocation, NYU, 15 December 1987 (Box 621, Folder 112)
  - Education Week commentary (Washington, D.C.), 15 December 1987 (Box 621, Folder 113)
  - Report to the Faculty Council, NYU, 17 December 1987 (Box 621, Folder 114)
  - Aspen Institute address (Berlin, Germany), 12 January 1988 (Box 622, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254691
  - Tribute to Norman Redlich, NYU Law Review, 12 January 1988 (Box 622, Folder 2)
  - Remarks on the American system of government, delivered before the Royal Institute of International Affairs (London, England), 14 January 1988 (Box 622, Folder 3)
  - Welcome remarks delivered at the Chief Academic Officers Photo Exhibition, NYU, 20 January 1988 (Box 622, Folder 4)
  - Remarks on education, delivered at the Conference on Teaching of Ethics (Ann Arbor, MI), 29 January 1988 (Box 622, Folder 6)
  - Remarks on higher education delivered before the Congressional Competitiveness Caucus (Washington, D.C.), 2 February 1988 (Box 622, Folder 7)
  - Remarks on the role of higher education, delivered as a speech before the ACCU (Palm Beach, FL), 2 February 1988 (Box 622, Folder 8)
  - Remarks delivered in Palm Beach, FL, 4-7 February 1988 (Box 622, Folder 9)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a luncheon honoring David Butler, NYU, 18 March 1988 (Box 622, Folder 10)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered as part of NYU in Albany, 22 March 1988 (Box 622, Folder 11)
  - Remarks delivered at a reception honoring Eli Evans, NYU, 21 March 1988 (Box 622, Folder 12)
  - Remarks delivered at a dinner meeting of the National Academy of Arts & Sciences, NYU, 23 March 1988 (Box 622, Folder 13)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a luncheon meeting of the Faculty Council, NYU, 23 March 1988 (Box 622, Folder 14)
  - Remarks on foreign policy delivered before the National Commission on American Foreign Policy, 29 March 1988 (Box 622, Folder 15)
  - Remarks delivered at a reception honoring NYU alumni (Philadelphia, PA), 30 March 1988 (Box 622, Folder 16)
  - Remarks delivered at a press conference announcing the Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies, NYU, 30 March 1988 (Box 622, Folder 17)
  - Remarks at a luncheon at the Metro Center, NYU, 31 March 1988 (Box 622, Folder 18)
  - Ditchley Foundations Conference, April-October 1988 (Box 622, Folder 19)
  - Brief remarks delivered at the Washington Square Park clean-up, 5 April 1988 (Box 622, Folder 20)
  - Welcome remarks delivered at a book party sponsored by NYU and the Spanish Institute, 6 April 1988 (Box 622, Folder 22)
  - Down Town Association, 20 April 1988 (Box 622, Folder 23)
  - Talking points for remarks delievered at the Congressional Arts Caucus Luncheon, NYU, 22 April 1988 (Box 622, Folder 25)
  - Founders Day Address, NYU, 24 April 1988 (Box 622, Folder 26)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Sir Peter Ramsbotham, NYU, 25 April 1988 (Box 622, Folder 27)
  - Remarks introducing Sir Peter Ramsbotham, NYU, 25 April 1988 (Box 622, Folder 28)
  - Brief remarks delivered before the Council on Economic Priorities, 26 April 1988 (Box 622, Folder 29)
  - Remarks at a luncheon announcing the NYU Law & Philanthropy Grant, 27 April 1988 (Box 622, Folder 30)
  - Remarks delivered at a dinner honoring David Kriser, 27 April 1988 (Box 622, Folder 31)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Mel Miller, 28 April 1988 (Box 622, Folder 32)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a CASH Luncheon, NYU, 28 April 1988 (Box 622, Folder 33)
  - Welcome remarks, NYU, 29 April 1988 (Box 622, Folder 34)
  - NYU Spring Celebration, 29 April 1988 (Box 622, Folder 35)
  - Commencement address, University of Charleston (Charleston, WV), 1 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 36)
  - Remarks on the politics of education delivered at a seminar on higher education, NYU, 2 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 37)
  - Tribute to Judge Weinfeld, NYU, 2 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 38)
  - Remarks on the value of public service delivered before the New York Federal Executive Board, 2 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 39)
  - Remarks delivered at a ceremony presenting the School of Education, Health, Nursing, and the Arts Professions Prism Award (NYC), 2 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 40)
  - Real Estate Institute Breakfast, NYU, 3 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 41)
  - Education Daily, Joe McGavin, May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 43)
  - Remarks delivered at the Casa Italiana Zerilli-Marimo, NYU, 9 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 44)
  - Welcome remarks before a meeting at the Visiting Mayors Urban Research Center, NYU, 12 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 46)
  - University Senate Report, NYU, 12 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 47)
  - Sweeney Scholarship Program Luncheon, NYU, 16 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 48)
  - 25-Year Service Awards, NYU, 17 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 49)
  - Dutch Treat Club Lunch (NYC), 17 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 50)
  - Alumni Council Dinner, NYU, 17 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 51)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered before a CREO Society concert, 18 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 52)
  - Remarks on the French Bicentennial, delivered at a luncheon at Le Cirque (NYC), 18 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 53)
  - Talking points for remarks about the NYU Community Fund, 19 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 54)
  - South Bend Boosters Hall of Fame (Notre Dame, IN), 21 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 55)
  - Commencement remarks, Fairleigh Dickinson University, 22 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 56)